Set music
Move mouse
Open fridge
Pickup kale
Put down kale
Pickup leeks
Put down leeks
Pickup fish cakes
Drop fish cake
Put fish cake on counter
Close fridge
Open oven
Put on oven gloves
Take out oven tray
Close oven
Put away oven gloves
Turn on stereo
Turn up volume
Open cupboard
take out kitchen foil
pull out kitchen foil
cut kitchen foil
put kitchen foil on hub
open cupboard
put away kitchen foil
close cupboard
fold kitchen foil
pick up knife
open fish cakes
put fish cakes on kitchen foil
throw away packaging
adjust fish cakes
open fish cake packets
turn off oven time
set oven timer
open fish cake packaging
pour fish cakes onto foil
throw away packaging
adjust fish cakes
pick up oven gloves
open oven
put tray into oven
close oven
put away oven gloves
set timer
pick up knife
open leek packaging
take out leeks
walk to sink
turn on tap
rinse leeks
shake off leeks
pick up chopping board
put down chopping board
move kale
pick up knife
adjust leeks
chop off leeks
pick up leek ends
throw away leek ends
pick up kettle
empty kettle
put water in kettle
turn off tap
put kettle onto boil
chop leeks
pickup leeks
rearrange leeks
chop leek
chop chop leek
Chop leek
Throw away leeks
Turn on tap
Rinse hands
Pick up pot
Turn on tap
Put pot on hob
Turn on hob
Pick up onion
Throw away packaging
Pick up leek
Put down leek
Pick up kale
Open kale package
pick up pot lid
put lid on pots
open cupboards
put away glass
put away bowl
put away slicer
pick up bowl
put away bowl
replace measuring drums
close cupboards
pick up sponge
turn on tap
Pour soap on sponge
Wash dish cover
Turn on tap
Wash plate
Wash glass
Put down glass
Pick up plate
Wash plate
wash plate
put down plate
pick up knife
wash knife
turn on tap
rinse knife
put away knife
rinse plate
put plate in drying rack
rinse glass
put away glass
rinse plate
put away plates
rinse plate cover
put away plate cover
turn off tap
shake off hands
rinse hands
rearrange plate cover
shake off hands
pick up kettle
open lid
pour water into pot
Pour water into pot
Put lid on pot
Put down kettle
Check timer
Set timer
Open fridge
Take out wine
Open cover it
Pick up wine glass
Close cover it
Put down wine glasses
Pick up bottle of wine
Open bottle of wine
Pour a glass of wine
Throw mail on the floor
Pick up glass of wine
Pour glass of wine
Drink glass of wine
Drink other glass of wine
Put bottle in the fridge
[END SUBTITLE]